ILR School Dean's Office Files /3085
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ILR School Dean's Office Files
1944-1980
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Ives, Irving M.
Emerson, Lynn A.
Neufeld, Maurice F.
Shank, Donald J.
Catherwood, Martin P.
/3085
29 cubic feet
29 linear ft.
Case files.
Consists primarily of correspondence, with some administrative records regarding undergraduate education and other matters.
3079938
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
R. Miles, January 13, 2016
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, September 20, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /3006: ILR School Dean's Office Publications /4014: ILR School Dean's Office Additional Files /4028: ILR School Dean's Office Additional Records /4054: ILR School Dean's Office Additional Files /4070: ILR School Dean's Office Additional Personnel Files /4082: ILR School Dean's Office Records /4100: ILR School Dean's Office "Report of the ILR Review Panel" Background Documentation /4144: ILR School Dean's Office Files Additional
Ives, Irving McNeil, 1896-1962; Emerson, Lynn A.; Neufeld, Maurice F.; Shank, Donald J.; Catherwood, M. P. (Martin Paul), 1904-1978; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations. Dean's Office; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations --Administration.
3079938
- PU-1-5 -- PU-1-6 1945-1947 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Summer Conference, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Summer School Teaching, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Questionnaire on Graduate Students, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- PU--thru 4 1945-1947 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- PR-1 through PR-3 1945-1947 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- PU-2-1 -- PU-2-3 1945-1947 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- PU-2-4-1 Preliminary Announcement 3-/31/44, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- PU-2-44 Announcements (by years), 1947 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- PU-2-5 Industrial + Labor Relations Reviews, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- PU-2-7-1 Extension Notes Vol. 1, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Staff Application A-D 1947-1948 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Staff Applications E-H 1947-1948 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Staff Applications J-R 1947-1948 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Staff Application S-Z 1947-1948 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Speakers 5-3-4, 1946-1947 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- 3089-2, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Memorandums, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Publications - Outside - Gen'l, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Memorandums, 1947-1950 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Library Letter Carbons + Lists, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Memorandums, 1947-1950 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- ST-1-1 Student, General, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- ST-1-3 Policy 1945-1947 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Speeches by Faculty Members, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Work Training Placements, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Graduate Placement ST-1-7, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- ST-2-1 Graduate Student General, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- ST-1-2 Curriculum, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- ST-2-2 Graduate Program + Planning 1945-1947 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Guest Lecturers S-3-6, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- S-3-3 Suggested Speakers 1947-1949 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- G-1-1 Several Members of the Faculty, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Several, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Several, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- G-1-1 Adams, Leonard, 1950 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Adams - Continued, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- G-1-1 Barton, Betty, 1951 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- G-1-1 Beach, C. Kenneth, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- G-1-1 Brooks, Earl, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Brooks (Con't), 1947 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- G-1-1 Brooks, Earl, 1951 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Brooks (con't), 1948 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- G-1-1 1945-1947 Earl Brooks (Box 3, Folder 12)
- G-1-1 Brophy, John, 1951 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- G-1-1 Burling, Temple, 1951 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- G-1-1 Campbell, James, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- R. Campbell (con't), 1949 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- G-1-1 Catherwood, Martin P., 1949 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- G--1 Campbell, Ralph, 1951 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- G-1-1 Clark, M. Gardner, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- G-1-1 Emerson, Eleanor, 1950 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- G-1-1 Emerson, Lynn, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- G-1-1 Ferguson, Robert, 1951 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- G-1-1 Foltman, F. F., 1949 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- G-1-1 Gordon, Paul, 1951 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- G-1-1 Hanson, C. Arnold, 1950 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Hanson (con't), 1949 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Hanson (con't), 1949 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- G-1-1 Hodges, Wayne, 1951 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- G-1-1, Hyatt Dave, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 29)
- G-1-1 Jehring, J. J., 1948 (Box 3, Folder 30)
- Jehring, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 31)
- G-1-1 Jensen, Vernon, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 32)
- Risley, (con't), 1949 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- G-1-1 Tolles, N. A., 1949 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- G-1-1 Stevenson, Doris, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- G-1-1 Smith, A. W., 1948 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- G-1-1 Whyte, W. F., 1949 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- G-1-1 Konvitz, Milton, 1949-1951 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- G-1-1 Kouzian, Ardemis, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- G-1-1 MacIntyre, Duncan, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- G-1-1 McCarthy, Phillip J., 1951 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- G-1-1 McConnell, John, 1947-1949 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- G-1-1 McKelvey, Jean T., 1951 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- G-1-1 Miller, J. G., 1948-1949 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- G-1-1 Morton, J. E., 1949 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- G-1-1 Neufield, M. F., 1949 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- G-1-1 Risley, Robert F., 1950 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Material to be refiled as per attached notes, 1948 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- G-1-2 A, 1949 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- G-1-2 B, 1947 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- B - (con't), 1949 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- G-1-2 C, 1949 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- C - (con't), 1949 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- C - (con't), 1949 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- G-1-2 D, 1948-1949 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- D - con't, 1949 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- G-1-2 E, 1949 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- G-1-2 F, 1949 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- G-1-2 G, 1948 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- G - Con't, 1949 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- G-1-2 H, 1948 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- H (con't), 1949 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- H (con't), 1948 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- G-1-2 I, 1949 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- G-1-2 K, 1949 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- S-2 M.P. Catherwood's Speeches - 1944-7, 1944-1947 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- S-2 M.P. Catherwood's Speeches - 1948 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- S-2 - M.P. Catherwood's Speeches - 1957-8, 1957-1958 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- S.2 M.P. Catherwood's Speeches - 1955-6, 1955-1956 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- S-2 M.P. Catherwood's - 1952-4, 1952-1954 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- S-2 M.P. Catherwood's Speeches - 1949-51, 1949-1951 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Speeches - M.P.C. (Extra Copies), 1946 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- 1949 NYSSILT Advisory Council (Box 7, Folder 1)
- A-4 State University of New York 1949 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- A-5-1 ILR Committees 1947-1949 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- A-8 NYSSILR Dean's Report to President, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- CU-2 Board of Trustees 1947-1949 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- ST-1-1 General, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- ST-2-1 General, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- ST-2-2 Program + Policy 1949 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- ST-2-3 Curriculum, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- ST-2-4 Fellowships 1948-1949 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- St-2-4b Industrial Psychiatry, 1948-1949 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- CU-4 Deans' Meeting 1946-49, 1946-1949 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- FS-1 General. Fiscal - ILR 1949 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- M-1 Meetings and Conferences - 1948-49, 1948-1949 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- R-1 General (1949) (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Research Projects for Foundation Grants, 1949 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Meeting attended by Faculty Outside, 1947 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Lecture Service, 1947-1948 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Conferences + Institutes 1945-1949 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- A-5-1 NYSSILR Committees (1950) (Box 9, Folder 1)
- CU-4 Dean's Meetings (1950) (Box 9, Folder 2)
- CU-12 University Faculty (1946-1950) (Box 9, Folder 3)
- "E-1. Extension General (1949-1950) Part 1 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- "E-1. Extension. General (1949-1950) Part 2 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- "E-1. Extension. General (1949-1950) Part 3 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- State University Forum - 1950 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- A-3 Advisory Council 1950+1951 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- A-4 State University 1951 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- A-5-1 ILR Committees 1951 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- CU-2 Board of Trustees 1950-51, 1950-1951 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- CU-4 Dean's Meeting 1951 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- CU-5 Graduate Faculty 1948-1951 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- E-1 Extension, General, 1951 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- ST - Bernard K. Allanson, 1955 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- ST - Jaynes Vogan Dunbar, 1959 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- ST - John Gordon McCabe, 1956 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- ST - Fred Martin Mintz, 1956 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- ST William Joseph Purdy, 1956 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- ST - Donald William Smith, 1956 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- ST - Naomi Spatz, 1956 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- ST - Robert Titus, 1956 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- ST - Eleanor L. Tum Suden, 1956 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- ST- John White, 1959 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- ST - Aly Sadek Agrama, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- ST - Sophia Rachael Alvarez, 1956 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- ST - Trevor Bain, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- ST - Richard H. Bowker, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 14)
- ST - J. John Chapman, 1955 (Box 11, Folder 15)
- ST - Alan Keith Collins, 1957-1959 (Box 11, Folder 16)
- ST - Claude J. Connally, 1954-1959 (Box 11, Folder 17)
- ST - Luciana Maria de Losi, 1958 (Box 11, Folder 18)
- ST - Arthur T. Edgerly, 1958 (Box 11, Folder 19)
- ST- Ibrahim A. El-Sherbini (Box 11, Folder 20)
- ST - John B. Ferguson, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 21)
- ST - John B. Ferguson, 1958 (Box 11, Folder 22)
- ST - Joan Kiel Finder, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 23)
- ST - Cesar Galileo Espinoza, 1955 (Box 11, Folder 24)
- ST - John Flagler, 1955 (Box 11, Folder 25)
- ST Eduardo F. Gonzales, 1954 (Box 11, Folder 26)
- ST - William H. Graham, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 27)
- ST - Roger Allan Graves, 1955 (Box 11, Folder 28)
- ST - Robert Judkins Hall (Box 11, Folder 29)
- ST - Patricia Hedges, 1956 (Box 11, Folder 30)
- ST - Robert D. Helsby, 1958 (Box 11, Folder 31)
- ST - John Thurow Hill, 1956 (Box 11, Folder 32)
- ST - William George Hosking, 1955 (Box 11, Folder 33)
- ST - Nawal Kapur, 1959 (Box 11, Folder 34)
- ST - Robert Adgar Kelley, 1955 (Box 11, Folder 35)
- ST - Gilbert Kostelec, 1958 (Box 11, Folder 36)
- ST - John F. B. Lawton, 1955 (Box 11, Folder 37)
- ST - John Wallace Leonard, 1958 (Box 11, Folder 38)
- ST - Karl G. Marning, 1956 (Box 11, Folder 39)
- ST - Richard Francis Martin, 1956 (Box 11, Folder 40)
- ST - Francis X. Mascola, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 41)
- ST - James Mendon Moore, 1956 (Box 11, Folder 42)
- ST - George H. Myers, 1959 (Box 11, Folder 43)
- ST - Braj Kishore Narayan, 1956 (Box 11, Folder 44)
- ST - Antonia Nell, 1956 (Box 11, Folder 45)
- ST - Carl Oles, 1956 (Box 11, Folder 46)
- ST - Thomas Patten, 1956 (Box 11, Folder 47)
- ST - Ronald A. Saldanha, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 48)
- ST - Thomas R. Shepard, 1955-1956 (Box 11, Folder 49)
- ST - Dona-Jane Spraggon, 1955 (Box 11, Folder 50)
- ST - B. Klare Sommers, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 51)
- ST - Elizabeth Jane Suttell, 1956 (Box 11, Folder 52)
- ST - Ram Tarneja, 1959 (Box 11, Folder 53)
- ST - Arthur N. Turner, 1958 (Box 11, Folder 54)
- ST - M. K. Varma, 1955 (Box 11, Folder 55)
- ST - Emory Washington, 1955 (Box 11, Folder 56)
- ST - Man Whisnant, 1956 (Box 11, Folder 57)
- G-1-2 Outside A, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- G-1-2 Outside B, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- G-1-2 Outside C, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- G-1-2 Outside D, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- G-1-2 Outside E, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- G-1-2 Outside E, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- G-1-2 Outside F, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- G-1-2 Outside G, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- G-1-2 Outside H, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- G-1-2 Outside I-J, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- G-1-2 Outside K, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- G-1-2 Outside L, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 12)
- G-1-2 Outside M, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- G-1-2 Outside N, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 14)
- G-1-2 Outside O-P, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 15)
- G-1-2 Outside Q-R, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 16)
- G-1-2 Outside S, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 17)
- G-1-2 Outside T, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 18)
- G-1-2 Outside U-V, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 19)
- G-1-2 Outside Y-Z, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 20)
- G-1-2 Outside W-X, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 21)
- G-1-2 Applicants, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 22)
- G-1-2 Outside A, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 23)
- G-1-2 Outside B, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 24)
- G-1-2 Outside C, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 25)
- G-1-2 Outside D, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 26)
- G-1-2 Outside E, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 27)
- G-1-2 Outside F, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 28)
- G-1-2 Outside G, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 29)
- G-1-2 Outside H, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 30)
- G-1-2 Outside I-J, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 31)
- G-1-2 Outside K, 1951 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- G-1-2 Outside L, 1951 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- G-1-2 Outside M, 1951 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- G-1-2 Outside N, 1951 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- G-1-2 Outside O-P, 1951 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- G-1-2 Outside Q-R, 1951 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- G-1-2 Outside S, 1951 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- G-1-2 Outside T, 1951 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- G-1-2 Outside T, 1951 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- G-1-2 Outside U-V, 1951 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- G-1-2 Outside W-X, 1951 (Box 13, Folder 11)
- G-1-2 Outside Y-Z, 1951 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- G-1-2 Applicants (Labor Law), 1952 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- G-1-2 A, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- G-1-2 B, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 15)
- G-1-2 C, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 16)
- G-1-2 D, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 17)
- G-1-2 E-F, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 18)
- G-1-2 G, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 19)
- G-1-2 H, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 20)
- G-1-2 I-J, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 21)
- G-1-2 K, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 22)
- G-1-2 L, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 23)
- G-1-2 M, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 24)
- G-1-2 N, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 25)
- G-1-2 O-P, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 26)
- G-1-2 Q-R, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 27)
- G-1-2 S, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 28)
- G-1-2 W-X-Y-Z, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 29)
- Publications, 1950-1951 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Review, 1950-1951 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- ECA French Project, 1951 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- ECA Norwegian Project, 1951 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- ECA Turkish Project, 1951 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- ST-1-1 General, 1951 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- ST-1-2 Undergraduate Curriculum, 1951 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- ST-1-4 Scholarships, 1951 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- ST-1-4a Father Kelley Scholarship, 1951 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- ST-1-5 Summer Session, 1951 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- ST-1-5a Summer Institutes, 1951 (Box 14, Folder 11)
- ST-1-5a Wage and Salary Conference, 1951 (Box 14, Folder 12)
- St-2-1 General, 1951 (Box 14, Folder 13)
- St-2-2 Program and Policy, 1950-1951 (Box 14, Folder 14)
- St-2-3 Curriculum, 1951 (Box 14, Folder 15)
- St-2-4 Fellowships, 1951 (Box 14, Folder 16)
- St-2-4a Assistantships, 1951 (Box 14, Folder 17)
- St-2-4b Industrial Psychiatry, 1950-1951 (Box 14, Folder 18)
- St-2-5 Foundations, 1951 (Box 14, Folder 19)
- Teachers' Conference, 1952 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Advisory Council Meeting, 1952 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Advisory Committee Meeting on Labor Educ., 1952 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Macy's Department Store Workers, 1952 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Institute of the Central N.Y. Regional Hospital Council, Inc., 1952 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Federal Labor Unions', AFL, 1952 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Savings Banks Association Conference, 1952 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Y.M.C.A. Institute June 16-20, 1952 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Institute for Training Specialists June 10-14, 1952 (Box 15, Folder 9)
- Training Directors Conference Oct. 9-10, 1952 (Box 15, Folder 10)
- Human Factors in Industrial Accident Prevention June 26 and 27, 1952 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- New York Central Railroad Conference April 14-17, 1952 (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Newsmen's Conference November 20-21, 1952 (Box 15, Folder 13)
- Administrative Conference, 1952 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- State University of N.Y., 1952 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- ILR Committees 1952 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- CU-2 Board of Trustees, 1952 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- CU-12 University Faculty 1951-1952 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- E-4 Committee on Labor Education, 1950-1952 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- E-1 General (1952) (Box 16, Folder 7)
- M-1 Institutes, 1951-1952 (Box 16, Folder 8)
- M-2 Summer Institutes, 1952 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- PU Publications Procedures and Policy, 1951-1952 (Box 16, Folder 10)
- PU-5-1 Review, 1952 (Box 16, Folder 11)
- Research Programs, 1949 (Box 16, Folder 12)
- R-1 Research General, 1951-1952 (Box 16, Folder 13)
- St-1-1 General, 1952 (Box 16, Folder 14)
- St-1-2 Undergraduate Curriculum, 1952 (Box 16, Folder 15)
- St-1-4 Scholarships, 1952 (Box 16, Folder 16)
- St-1-4a Father Kelley Scholarships, 1952 (Box 16, Folder 17)
- St-2-2 General, 1952 (Box 16, Folder 18)
- St-2-2 Program and Policy, 1952 (Box 16, Folder 19)
- St-2-3 Curriculum, 1952 (Box 16, Folder 20)
- St-2-4 Fellowships, 1952 (Box 16, Folder 21)
- St-2-4a Assistantships, 1952 (Box 16, Folder 22)
- St-2-5 Foundations, 1952 (Box 16, Folder 23)
- University Newsletters, 1949-1952 (Box 16, Folder 24)
- Summer Sessions - 1952 (Box 16, Folder 25)
- Visit of the Board of Trustees of the State University of New York, 1949 (Box 16, Folder 26)
- German Program, 1951-1952 (Box 16, Folder 27)
- G-1-1 Dean M. P. Catherwood, 1957-1959 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- G-1-1 Paul H. Boorman, 1958 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- G-1-1 Walter Leibowitz, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 3)
- G-1-1 Robert McCarthy, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- G-1-1 John MacKinnon, 1958 (Box 17, Folder 5)
- G--1 George Myers, 1958 (Box 17, Folder 6)
- G-1-1 Bernie Oltz, 1956 (Box 17, Folder 7)
- G-1-1 Barbara Proctor, 1958-1959 (Box 17, Folder 8)
- CU-7 University Faculty Meetings, 1957-1958 (Box 17, Folder 9)
- CU-7 University Faculty Meetings, 1956-1957 (Box 17, Folder 10)
- CU-7 University Faculty Meetings 1953-54 and 1955-56, 1953-1956 (Box 17, Folder 11)
- M-1-1 Special Programs -- Residential Club Lease Sept. 1957- Sept. 1959, 1957-1959 (Box 17, Folder 12)
- M-1-1 Special Programs -- Residential Club Lease 1956 to June 1957, 1956-1957 (Box 17, Folder 13)
- M-10 Special Program Promotion, 1958 (Box 17, Folder 14)
- M-10 Special Program Promotion, 1958 (Box 17, Folder 15)
- M-11 Conference Supplies and Materials, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 16)
- M-13-1 Special Programs -- Housing, Rooms and Reservations, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 17)
- M-7 Albert Martin, 1958 (Box 17, Folder 18)
- M-7 Ellen McDonald Conference Recorder, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 19)
- M-7 Ellen McDonald, Conference Recorder, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 20)
- M-7 Sally Sandidge, Conference Secretary, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 21)
- M-7 Marie L. Burba, Conference Secretary, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 22)
- M-7 Jane Cantlay, Conference Recorder, 1956 (Box 17, Folder 23)
- M-7 Elizabeth Hough, 1954 (Box 17, Folder 24)
- G-1-2 K, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- G-1-2 L, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 2)
- G-1-2 M, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 3)
- G-1-2 N, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 4)
- G-1-2 O-P, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- G-1-2 Q-R, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 6)
- G-1-2 S, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 7)
- G-1-2 T, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 8)
- G-1-2 U-V, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 9)
- G-1-2 W-X, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 10)
- G-1-2 Y-Z, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 11)
- Several Members of Faculty, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 12)
- G-1-1 Adams, Leonard, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 13)
- G-1-1 Aronson, Robert, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 14)
- G-1-1 Brophy, John, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 15)
- G-1-1 Brooks, Earl, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 16)
- G-1-1 Burling, Temple, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 17)
- G-1-1 Campbell, James, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 18)
- G-1-1 Campbell, Ralph, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 19)
- G-1-1 Catherwood, Martin, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 20)
- G-1-1 Clark, M. Gardner, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 21)
- G-1-1 Cook, Alice, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 22)
- G-1-1 Cullen, Donald, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 23)
- G-1-1 Emerson, Eleanor, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 24)
- G-1-1 Emerson, Lynn, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 25)
- G-1-1 Ferguson, Robert, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 26)
- G-1-1 Foltman, Felician, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 27)
- G-1-1 Frank, Richard, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 28)
- G-1-1 Goodman, Eleanor, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 29)
- G-1-1 Gordon, Richard, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 30)
- G-1-1 Gray, Lois, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 31)
- G-1-1 Hanson, C. A., 1954 (Box 18, Folder 32)
- G-1-1 Hodges, Wayne, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 33)
- G-1-1 Jensen, Vernon, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 34)
- G-1-1 Konvitz, Milton, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 35)
- G-1-1 MacIntyre, Duncan, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 36)
- G-1-1 McCarthy, Philip, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 37)
- G-1-1 McConnell. John, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 38)
- G-1-1 McKelvey, Jean, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 39)
- G-1-1 Miller, J. Gormly, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 40)
- G-1-1 Miller, Frank, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 41)
- G-1-1 Morrison, Riley, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 42)
- G-1-1 Morton, Joseph, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 43)
- G-1-1 Neufield, Maurice, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 44)
- G-1-1 Ornati, Oscar, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 45)
- G-1-1 Perlman, Mark, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 46)
- G-1-1 Perrins, Harlan, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 47)
- G-1-1 Raimon, Robert, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 48)
- G-1-1 Risley, Robert, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 49)
- G-1-1 Smith, Alpheus, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 50)
- G-1-1 Smith, Alphaeus, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 51)
- G-1-1 Tolles, N. Arnold, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 52)
- G-1-1 Whyte, William, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 53)
- G-1-1 Windmuller, John, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 54)
- G-1-1 Several Members of Faculty, 1955 (Box 18, Folder 55)
- G-1-1 Adams, Leonard, 1955 (Box 18, Folder 56)
- G-1-1 Aronson, Robert L., 1955 (Box 18, Folder 57)
- G-1-1 Elumen, Isadore, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 58)
- G-1-1 Brophy, John M., 1955 (Box 18, Folder 59)
- G-1-1 Burling, Temple, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 60)
- G-1-1 Campbell, James, 1955 (Box 18, Folder 61)
- G-1-1 Campbell, Ralph, 1955 (Box 18, Folder 62)
- G-1-1 Carpenter, Jesse T., 1955 (Box 18, Folder 63)
- G-1-1 Catherwood, M. P., 1955 (Box 18, Folder 64)
- G-1-1 Clark, W. Gardner, 1955 (Box 18, Folder 65)
- G-1-1 Cook, Alice, 1955 (Box 18, Folder 66)
- G-1-1 Cullen, Donald, 1955 (Box 18, Folder 67)
- G-1-1 Donovan, Ronald (Box 18, Folder 68)
- G-1-1 Emerson, Eleanor, 1955 (Box 18, Folder 69)
- G-1-1 Ferguson, Robert, 1955 (Box 18, Folder 70)
- G-1-1 Foltman, F. F., 1955 (Box 18, Folder 71)
- G-1-1 Frank, Richard, 1955 (Box 18, Folder 72)
- G-1-1 Gordon, Richard, 1955 (Box 18, Folder 73)
- G-1-1 Gray, Lois S., 1955 (Box 18, Folder 74)
- G-1-1 Hanson, C. A., 1955 (Box 18, Folder 75)
- G-1-1 Hodges, Wayne L., 1955 (Box 18, Folder 76)
- G-1-1 Jensen, Vernon, 1955 (Box 18, Folder 77)
- G-1-1 Kaufman, Jacob J., 1955 (Box 18, Folder 78)
- G-1-1 Konvitz, Milton R., 1955 (Box 18, Folder 79)
- G-1-1 MacIntrye, Duncan, 1955 (Box 18, Folder 80)
- G-1-1 McCarthy, Phillip, 1955 (Box 18, Folder 81)
- G-1-1 McConnell, John, 1955 (Box 18, Folder 82)
- G-1-1 McKelvey, Jean T., 1955 (Box 18, Folder 83)
- G-1-1 Miller, Frank, 1955 (Box 18, Folder 84)
- G-1-1 Miller, J. Gormly, 1955 (Box 18, Folder 85)
- G-1-1 Morris, James, 1955 (Box 18, Folder 86)
- G-1-1 Neufield, Maurice, 1955 (Box 18, Folder 87)
- G-1-1 Riley Morrison, 1955 (Box 18, Folder 88)
- G-1-1 Ornati, Oscar, 1955 (Box 18, Folder 89)
- G-1-1 Perrins, Harlan, 1955 (Box 18, Folder 90)
- G-1-1 Radom, Matthew, 1955 (Box 18, Folder 91)
- G-1-1 Raisley, Robert F., 1955 (Box 18, Folder 92)
- G-1-1 Slavick, Fred, 1955 (Box 18, Folder 93)
- G-1-1 Smith, Alpheus, 1955 (Box 18, Folder 94)
- G-1-1 Tolles, N. Arnold, 1955 (Box 18, Folder 95)
- G-1-1 Whyte, William F., 1955 (Box 18, Folder 96)
- G-1-1 Windmuller, John, 1955 (Box 18, Folder 97)
- G-1-1 Wohlking, Wallace, 1955 (Box 18, Folder 98)
- G-1-1 Skyre, J. Woodrow, 1955 (Box 18, Folder 99)
- M-1 Institutes, 1950 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- ST-1-1 General, 1950 (Box 19, Folder 2)
- St-1-2 Undergraduate Curriculum, 1949-1950 (Box 19, Folder 3)
- ST-1-4a Father Kelley Scholarship, 1949-1950 (Box 19, Folder 4)
- ST-1-5a Personal Admin. Seminar, 1950 (Box 19, Folder 5)
- ST-2-5 Foundations (1949-1950) (Box 19, Folder 6)
- Guidance Inspection Training Course Handbook (Box 19, Folder 7)
  Scope and Contents
  Bound